Anish Fathima

Engineer

Dedicated and efficient engineer offering 5+ years of experience in Full stack Web Development and in building interactive and user centered web design to scale. Well-organized and customer-focused with proven skills in development, project management and team leadership. Aiming to utilize skills in achieving goals. Seeking to further improve the skills.

Work History

2019-05 -Current

Engineer

Infoview Technologies Pvt Ltd, Chennai, Tamilnadu

- Managed team of 5 for layout improvisation using javascript and jquery.
- Engaged in analyzing client's requirements and implemented business flow for Supply Chain Management process.
- Worked in **Angular** for creating components.

2015-06 -2019-05

Trainee Engineer

Infoview Technologies Pvt Ltd, Chennai, Tamilnadu

- Developed full stack web pages using HTML5, CSS3,
 Javascript which processed, analyzed and rendered data...
- Managed on time delivery of projects.
- Worked in backend technologies such as core java and java8 using spring framework and springboot
- Planned and engineered **RESTful web services** to manipulate dynamic datasets.
- Created UI components using XML and google closure framework.
- Handled Databases such as MySQL and Postgres.

Education

2011-06 -2015-05

B.Tech: Information Technology

Sri Ramakrishna Institute Of Technology - Coimbatore

Contact

Address

Ooty, TN, 643001

Phone

763 998 4453

E-mail

anishsrit2911@gmail.com

Skills

HTML,CSS3, Javascript



Angular and jquery



Java basics and core java



Java8



Google Closure framework



SQL and Postgres databases

